getcrackin.com 2016-06-27

# 

### **Wonderful® Pistachios Privacy Policy**

Your privacy is important to Wonderful Pistachios & Almonds LLC (“we” or “us”). To better protect your privacy, we provide this notice explaining our privacy practices and the choices you can make about the ways in which information about you is collected and used at www.wonderfulpistachios.com (the “Site”). We encourage you to read and review the terms of this Privacy Policy before using the Site. By using the Site, you agree to accept the terms of our Privacy Policy. If you do not agree with any part of this Privacy Policy, please do not use the Site.

#### INFORMATION WE COLLECT

#### _Personally Identifiable Information_

To fulfill your requests for information, enable you to participate in our product offerings or to upload your resume on our Careers webpage, and provide you with opportunities to learn about other products and services in which we think you might be interested, we ask that you provide us with certain personally identifiable information. The types of personally identifiable information that may be collected include: name, address, e-mail address, telephone number, fax number, date of birth, employment information and information related to your education, training, list of references, and information about your interests in and use of various products, programs, and services. By providing your personal information on the Site, you consent to allow us to use that information in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

In some instances, we may request that you submit information about other people. For example, if you wish to share information from the Site with another person, you might submit the recipient’s name and e-mail address or mailing address; or if you include references, you might submit the reference’s name and e-mail address. The types of personally identifiable information that may be collected about other people include: recipient’s name, address, e-mail address, and telephone number.

Any information you disclose voluntarily on the Site or in any forum, blogs or other public areas that we may develop in the future becomes public information. We cannot control the actions of the Site users and advise you to use your discretion in sharing information about yourself on the Internet. All information sharing is optional and done so at your own risk.

#### _Non-Personally Identifiable Information_

We also may collect certain non-personally identifiable information when you visit many of our webpages on the Site, such as the type of browser you are using (e.g., Google Chrome, Firefox, Internet Explorer), the type of operating system you are using, (e.g., Windows Vista, Mac OS), the domain name of your Internet service provider (e.g., Time Warner Cable, Comcast, AT&T), the name of the webpages you visit, the time you access our webpages, and the length of time you stay on those pages. 

We collect this information in order to determine which areas of the Site are most popular and to enhance your experience with the Site. This information may also be shared with third parties on an aggregate and non-personally identifiable basis. However, please be assured that this information will in no way personally identify you or any other visitors of the Site.

The Site may use third party analytics services. Such services may record mouse clicks, mouse movements, scrolling activities as well as any text you type in the Site. These services do not collect personally identifiable information that you do not voluntarily enter in the Site. The services do not track your browsing habits across websites which do not use such services.

#### HOW WE USE THE INFORMATION

We use your personally identifiable information to provide the requested information or content, respond to your inquiries about our offerings, respond to a comment made on the Site or our blog, offer you other products, programs or services that we believe may be of interest to you, or for other purposes disclosed at the time of collection. We also may use your personally identifiable information to contact you regarding your use of our products or services, or regarding changes to our Privacy Policy, or other policies or terms that affect you and your use of the Site or our products and services. In addition, we may use such information to improve the content and navigation of the Site, or for other internal purposes. 

We use the information that you provide about others to enable us to send them information. From time to time, we also may use this information to offer our products, programs, or services to them.

Agents and contractors who have access to personally identifiable information are required to protect this information in a manner that is consistent with this Privacy Policy by, for example, not using the information for any purpose other than to carry out the services they are performing for us.

We may utilize third-party applications to process our online employment applications and submissions; however, the handling of personal information shall be governed by this Privacy Policy.

Although we take appropriate measures to safeguard against unauthorized disclosures of information, we cannot assure you that personally identifiable information that we collect will never be disclosed in a manner that is inconsistent with this Privacy Policy.

#### INFORMATION SHARING

Information collected from the Site under this Privacy Policy is shared among and used by us and The Wonderful Company LLC and its affiliates.

We may, from time to time, share personally identifiable information with other companies affiliated with us and unrelated third parties (e.g., retailers, marketers) to enable them to provide users with opportunities to learn of products or services in which they may be interested. You should also be aware that this means that we may transfer information to any country in the world, including the United States and other countries that may not offer the same level of data protection as the country where you reside. Please see the “Your Choices” section below for more information on how you can express your preferences regarding our sharing of information. 

We also may disclose personally identifiable information in the following instances:

_Legal Action:_ We may disclose information about our users, including personally identifiable information, when legally required to do so, at the request of governmental authorities conducting an investigation, to verify or enforce compliance with the policies governing the Site or applicable laws, or to protect against misuse or unauthorized use of the Site. We also may disclose user information whenever we believe disclosure is necessary to limit our legal liability; to protect or defend our rights or property; or protect the safety, rights, or property of our users.

_Corporate Change:_ We may sell, transfer, or otherwise disclose user information, including personally identifiable information, to a successor entity in connection with a corporate merger, consolidation, asset sale, or other corporate change or combination of assets involving us.

In addition, we may disclose anonymous, aggregated user statistics to third parties for a variety of purposes. For example, we may disclose how many individuals visited certain areas of the Site, how many men or women receive our newsletter, or other demographic data about users of our products or services. 

#### YOUR CHOICES

As noted above, we may use the personally identifiable information we collect from you to offer you products and services that may be of interest to you. If you would like to opt out of future communications and/or promotional materials from us, you may indicate this preference by following the unsubscribe instructions at the end of e-mail communications, by logging into your account and changing your communication preferences, or by sending us an e-mail at legalinfo.pistachiosandalmonds@wonderful.com to request any change in your communication preferences. 

As also noted above, we may, from time to time, share personally identifiable information with companies whose practices are not covered by this Privacy Policy (e.g., other marketers, retailers, participatory databases, and non-profit organizations) that want to market products or services to you.  To request that we not share your information for such marketing purposes, you may log into your profile and change your account preferences accordingly or e-mail us at legalinfo@paramountfarms.com.

As also noted above, we may, from time to time, share personally identifiable information with companies whose practices are not covered by this Privacy Policy (e.g., other marketers, retailers, participatory databases, and non-profit organizations) that want to market products or services to you. To request that we not share your information for such marketing purposes, you may log into your profile and change your account preferences accordingly or e-mail us at legalinfo.pistachiosandalmonds@wonderful.com.

#### COOKIES & WEB BEACONS

To enhance your experience with the Site, many of our webpages use “cookies.” Cookies are text files we place in your computer’s browser to store your preferences. Cookies, by themselves, do not tell us your e-mail address or other personally identifiable information unless you choose to provide this information to us by, for example, registering at the Site. However, once you choose to furnish the site with personally identifiable information, this information may be linked to the data stored in the cookie.

We use cookies to understand site usage and to improve the content and offerings on the Site. For example, we may use cookies to personalize your experience at our webpages (e.g., to recognize you by name when you return to the Site), save your password in password-protected areas, and enable you to use shopping carts on the Site. We also may use cookies to offer you products, programs, or services. 

Cookies do not cause damage to your computer systems or files, and only the website that transferred a particular cookie to you can read, modify or delete such cookie. You always have the option of disabling cookies using your browser preferences. Most browsers allow you to delete existing cookies, to automatically decline cookies or to be given the choice of declining or accepting the transfer of particular cookies to your computer. However, please be aware that some features of the Site may not function properly or may be slower if you refuse cookies. We do not control cookies that you may occasionally get from third-party sites.

“Web beacons” or clear .gifs are small pieces of code placed on a webpage to monitor the behavior of and collect data about the visitors viewing a webpage. For example, Web beacons can be used to count the users who visit a webpage or to deliver a cookie to the browser of a visitor viewing that page. We may use Web beacons from third party Web analytics services on this Site from time to time for these and other purposes. The service does not collect any personally identifiable information that you do not voluntarily enter in this Site.

#### COLLECTION OF INFORMATION BY THIRD-PARTY SITES AND SPONSORS

We may, from time to time, offer content (e.g., contests, sweepstakes, or promotions) that is sponsored by or co-branded with identified third parties, including affiliated businesses. By virtue of these relationships, the third parties may obtain personally identifiable information that visitors voluntarily submit to participate in the site activity. We have no control over these third parties’ use of this information. Since these third parties will use your information in accordance with their own privacy practices, you should check their websites for information regarding their privacy policies. We will notify you at the time of requesting personally identifiable information if these third parties will obtain such information.

We may use a reputable third party to present or serve the advertisements that you may see at our webpages. These third-party ad servers may use cookies, Web beacons, clear .gifs, or similar technologies to help present such advertisements, and to help measure and research the advertisements’ effectiveness. The use of these technologies by these third-party ad servers is subject to their own privacy policies and is not covered by our Privacy Policy. 

We and our advertisers may use third parties to serve or present the ads that appear on the Site and to conduct research about the advertisements. For more information about third-party ad servers, please visit: www.networkadvertising.org. 

#### LINKS TO OTHER SITES

The Site may contain links to other sites that are not operated by us and whose information practices may be different than ours. You should consult the other sites’ privacy notices as we have no control over information that is submitted to, or collected by, these third parties. We are not responsible for the privacy practices of these other sites and cannot guarantee the security of any of your personal information collected there.

#### OUR COMMITMENT TO DATA SECURITY

We have put in place physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and help prevent unauthorized access to, maintain security of, and correctly use the information we collect. Personally identifiable information and account activity are also protected through the use of e-mail addresses and passwords. In order to maintain the security of your information, you should protect the confidentiality of such information used on the Site or to log into your account, if applicable. Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we strive to protect your personal information and privacy, we cannot guarantee or warrant the security of any information you disclose or transmit to us online and cannot be responsible for the theft, destruction, or inadvertent disclosure of your personal information.

#### HOW YOU CAN ACCESS AND UPDATE INFORMATION

If you have previously provided any personally identifiable information to us by way of the Site, you retain the right to review, correct, update, delete or otherwise modify such information.

To access the personally identifiable information that we have collected about you that we maintain, or to correct factual errors in such information, simply log into your account using your e-mail address and password to update your information. Or you may also contact us at the “Contact” address, telephone number or e-mail provided below.

To protect your privacy and security, we will take reasonable steps to help verify your identity before granting access or making corrections.

#### INTERNATIONAL VISITORS

Information we collect will be transferred to and processed in the United States where our central database is operated. The privacy laws of the U.S. may not be as comprehensive as the data protection laws of the European Union and elsewhere. Please be assured that we take reasonable steps to ensure that your privacy is protected and implement necessary measures on an ongoing basis to keep your personal information secure. By providing us with your personally identifiable information, you consent to its use in accordance with this Privacy Policy, including the transfer of personally identifiable information relating to you to our computer systems in the United States. 

#### PRIVACY POLICY FOR MINORS

We do not knowingly collect information from minors.  If you are under the age of 18, we request that you do not provide any personally identifiable information to us.

#### UPDATES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY

From time to time, we reserve the right to make updates to this Privacy Policy. We will notify you about material changes in the way we treat personally identifiable information by, for example, placing a notice on the Site. We encourage you to periodically check back and review this Privacy Policy so that you always will know what information we collect, how we use it, and to whom we disclose it. Your continued use of the Site following any changes to this Privacy Policy will be deemed to constitute your acceptance of such change.

#### HOW TO CONTACT US

If you have any questions or concerns about this Privacy Policy or its implementation, you may contact us at: 

Wonderful Pistachios & Almonds LLC  
11444 West Olympic Boulevard  
Los Angeles, California 90064  
Attention: Chief Legal Officer  
Facsimile: (310) 966-5758  
E-mail: legalinfo.pistachiosandalmonds@wonderful.com 

© 2015 Wonderful Pistachios & Almonds LLC. All rights reserved.
